how's it going [ __ ] Timbers one two
three four five filled with a very
special video today so one of my fans
sent me a link to this I don't know I
question as a thing and it picks out
your favorite Sonic Underground
character which is really cool a penalty
contains most of the main characters of
Sonic Underground not all of them
unfortunately but yeah it's Sonic
undergone it's not that well-known so
what are you gonna do not if not
everyone's gonna know every main
character you know killers like Jared
and all that [ __ ] so I think it's time
to get started so battle number one
Bobby Orr Mindy's dad well I think
that's pretty obvious [ __ ] bowel be
00 this shit's getting tough Sonic vs
manny the battle the Battle of bras
Sonic is so cool like but man heat Max a
[ __ ] badass socks Bobby's [ __ ]
soldier should I pick Sonic net mannix
hell is kind of cool though [ __ ] I I
like both min divas team was me five
were like let's be with mean he's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] butchers bountiful Bob will
be the song good Chuck come on now like
really Bobby was Uncle Chuck you who the
[ __ ] is got pickle good shot [ __ ] Bobby
[ __ ] Oh Mindy Uncle Chuck buses
Mindy's dad too damn I just I don't know
I don't know well Mindy's daddy he's a
badass like Uncle Chuck I me a chill I
got
Uncle Chuck looks like Sonic with a
mustache like [ __ ] Queen Aleena this is
the KKnux do a wheelie I gotta go with my
man KKnux like [ __ ] sorry of us a Sonic
net it's really Sonia cut you you need
you can thing you can challenge your bro
Bobby vez cameras only 4500 [ __ ] oh my
[ __ ] God oh [ __ ] Bobby's got big ass
look he's got money to and came with
only five great you two child eat you
know gotta [ __ ] [ __ ] sock is Bobby's
[ __ ] [ __ ] i'll decide later about like
both bridges Uncle Chuck this is Mindy
hot [ __ ] now really now really Uncle
Chuck Mindy's a [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] Uncle
Chuck [ __ ] come on now Oh Mindy vasa
death Mindy's got such big boobs but
mean he's dead I please always got fine
ass Oh was that socks adopt his dad who
had the fine ass it I gotta go with
Mindy she's got big boobs she got big
butt to Sonic vs not exactly [ __ ] socks
Bobby's [ __ ] but I know cuz it's so
cool though Knuckles came over to my
house and we made waffles last week so
I'm gonna feel bad if I don't pick nogs
[ __ ]
saara KKnux oh [ __ ] okay then Knuckles
[ __ ] Sonia versus Queen Aleena name
is feeling of Lena too who is that
that's not Queen Aleena [ __ ] like a GOG
[ __ ] I don't know I like both of them
God go with Sonia like [ __ ] her name's i
misspelled oh [ __ ] Sonic vs Bobby really
Wilma Gaga with Bob up in this [ __ ]
Sonic vs Uncle Chuck Charles muster sock
the Hedgehog oh my God God go with the
fat [ __ ] Knuckles is all good shot okay
then God go with Knuckles Sonia bazonga
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] about this hoe
I don't care God go with Uncle Chuck
[ __ ] Sonia vs me really why is me
even on this [ __ ] list oh I see why
now does the Miss Cooke Queen Aleena
again sorry Mindy night that can help
you this hand oh that was it what would
the food put the food boss it I like
both of the bobbing tv5 what the [ __ ]
what is Bobby number 10 know that the
tire ok nuk sock neck of Todd for one
two three who's number two who's losing
up to so fun k then [ __ ] I think this
is pretty accurate I get
yes I think it's pretty good probably
your place Mindy and Mindy's dad and
then you got pretty good accurate up in
this [ __ ] I think I'm done okay I'm
done hope you had fun [ __ ] cuz I sure
did boom